Tim Vlasuk

timvlasuk@gmail.com Bellingham, WA

Remote Engineer

GitHub LinkedIn Portfolio

Summary

Self motivated continual learner that has 3+ years working within software development teams with a focus on quality assurance. Experience applying broad view perspective with ability to write and understand code to contribute within the Product Lifecycle.

Work Experience

<u>BeFunky</u> Remote

Senior QA Engineer

Dec 2020 - Present

- Follow features and bug fixes through software development cycle for weekly web releases.
- Cross Device test packaged app for release in AppStore and PlayStore.
- Collaborate with Product and Dev teams to define scope and ensure expectations are met and tracked.
- Observe trends and troubleshoot issues using Mixpanel, Sentry, and GA4.
- Engage with entire team to brainstorm and contribute to product vision and growth.
- Monitor existing Checkly and WebDriverIO tests; collaborate with devs to update tests when needed.

Bigtincan Remote

QA Engineer Dec 2019 – Dec 2020

- Ensured webApp passes local build and deployment to staging servers.
- Ran manual regression testing on web app, crm integration, and mail client add-ins.
- Pulled custom data reports in Django Shell and automated when possible.
- Worked closely with support and dev teams to trouble-shoot, document, and resolve bugs.
- Contributed to exploratory testing campaign comparing Cypress, NightwatchJS, and Postman/Newman.

Nielsen Brother Inc

Shop Tech

Sedro-Woolley, WA

April 2014 - Dec 2017

- Maintained mechanic shop environment.
- Assisted in maintenance and repair of gas, diesel, and hydraulic equipment.
- Consolidated multiple loose roles into one.

Skills

Front End: JavaScript ES6+, React, Redux, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SEO/WebVitals *Back End:* Node.js, Express.js, Django, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, RESTful APIs, Heroku

Testing: Mocha, Chai, Enzyme, Travis CI, Postman, Newman-cli

Environment Tools: Python, Git, Gitlab, Docker, Unix/Linux, OSI Model, Bash, Virtual Box Experience Using: GA4, Mixpanel, zenDesk, Sentry, Jira, Salesforce, Checkly, WebDriverIO

Education

THINKFUL 2018-2019

Full-Stack Web Development Program / Engineering Immersion

- Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards with a focus on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Redux, and algorithms & data structures.
- Created and deployed mobile-first applications while learning new languages and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a senior web developer.